Guide to the Max Wilk Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2009 Acquisition, 1735-2007; 37; 20.02; (19 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Audio recordings
    - Audiocassettes, 1939-2002
      - "Box #2: Famous People", 1949-1993
        - "Danny Kaye-Max Wilk-Sylvia Fine, Kissing Noodles; Danny Kaye-Barbara and Max Wilk (cooking lesson)", 1974 July 12; 1 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002104610531)
        - "Yale Reunion-Max Wilk (1941), Panel Discussion: Cultural Implication of Reaganism, David and Max Wilk; questions", 1981 May 30; 1 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002104610549)
        - "Moran/Mack, Vaudeville; (1949) Irving Berlin-Singing 'The Honorable Profession of the Fourth Estate' 'Just One Way to Say I Love You', Abbott and Costello", undated; 1 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002104610556)
        - "Henry Senber, re: Federal Theatre, N.Y.- Players", 1983 January 11; 1 (Box 108, Item barcode 39002104610564)
        - "Sylvia Fine/Max Wilk Conf. re: Kissinger Noodles", 1974 July 12; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610234)
        - "Max Wilk Library", 1986 January 21; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610242)
        - "Harold Sack, NY; Brown, Goddard, Secretary", 1993 January 12; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610259)
        - "Tamara Geva, NY, LA; Ziegfeld-1929,", 1992 April 1; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610267)
        - "Ed Hartman, Santa Fe, NM: Strike Me Pink, 1932-on", 1991 August 5; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610275)
        - "Anne Edwards, Westport", 1985 March 22; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610283)
        - "Jonathan Winters", 1967; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610291)
        - "Ed Wynn, L.A., Sides 1 & 2", 1960 August 9; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610309)
        - "Ed Wynn, Sides 3 & 4", [1960]; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610317)
        - "Ed Wynn Sides 3 & 4", [1960]; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610325)
        - "Al Hirschfeld, Sweet Bye And Bye-1946, re: S.J. Perelman, Vernon Duke, Ogden Nash, NY", 1993 October 21; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610333)
        - "Lucille Kalien", undated; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610341)
        - "Kay Swift, Frankie-Gershwin", 1989 March 30; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610358)
        - "Audrey Wood tributes: 1/Gielgud, 2/Mason, 3/Gish", undated; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610366)
        - "Maxine Sullivan/Miss Otis Regrets", 1987 March 22; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610374)
        - "AW/TW -L. Hunt-N. Lane, New York", 1990 March 19 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610382)
        - "WPA tribute, NY-Broadway Theatre", 1982 October 4; 1 (Box 109, Item barcode 39002104610390)
        - "Sam Leve", New York, 1983 January 8; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975301)
          re: Hallie Flanagan and Federal Theatre
        - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood", New York, 1991 November 25; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975319)
          Includes Linda Hunt, Nathan Lane
        - "Mercer Memorial", 1976 July 22; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975327)
          Includes: Margaret Whiting, Harold Arlen, Al Higgler, Jimmy Rowles, Bing Crosby, Dinah Shore, Mel Torme, Fred Estaire, Carl Rowan, Cliff Robertson
        - "Broadway Applauds Lincoln Center, I & II", 1986 April 14; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975335)
        - "Broadway Applauds Lincoln Center, III", 1986 April 14; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975343)
        - "Irving Berlin, Early Music", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975350)
        - "Berlin '78s -side A '30's", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975368)
      - "Box #3: Film and Music Interviews", 1947-1998
        - "Follow the Crowd", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975376)
          Sang by Irving Berlin
        - "Berlin 1909-1979", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975384)
        - "Berlin, BBC I & II", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975392)
        - "Berlin, BBC III-IV", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975400)
        - "Berlin, BBC V", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975418)
        - "Irving Berlin Vaudeville Songs", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975426)
        - "Berlin-Vaudeville, II", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975434)
        - "Irving Berlin, pre-1912 vaudeville", undated; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975442)
        - "Theo Bikel, NY", 1997 December 2; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975459)
        - " The Cosby Show, guests Jolson / Berlin", 1947 May 7; 1 (Box 110, Item barcode 39002109975467)
        - "Bert Lahr Sketches, Jimmy Durante", undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975475)
          Annotation includes sketch, monologues, "I Want An Old Fashinoed Girl", and "Friendship"
        - "Bert Lahr, (Max Wilk), Durante (Finish)", undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975483)
        - "Saul Chaplin", 1997 October 13; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975491)
        - "Anna Crouse, 'Sound of Music',NY", 1997 October 9; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975509)
        - "Ernie Lehman, 'Sound of Music'", 1997 October 15; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975517)
        - "Bob Wise", 1997 October 16; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975525)
        - "Frank Goodman", 1996 October 7; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975533)
        - "Lorn Peters", 1998 October 14 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975541)
        - "Susan H. Shulman", 1997 December 2; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975558)
        - "Jule Styne - preface to They're Playing Our Song", 1986 June 16; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975566)
        - "WNYC - Lopate interviews Wilk", 1998 January 8; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975574)
      - "Box #4: Music and Rarities", 1961-1993
        - "Bolcom and Morris, Berlin broadcast", undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975582)
        - "Duke Ellington's Funeral-Alice Babs 'Heaven'", undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975590)
        - "June Havoc, I Guess I'll Have to Telegraph My Baby", undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975608)
        - "'Foxy' Demos - Sung by Mercer (from Ian McLellan Hunter tape), undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975616)
        - "Oklahoma, background", 1990; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975624)
        - "David Lamarche & Others, A Tribute to Ogden Nash, The Century Club, NY", 1993 February 22; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975632)
        - "Merman V. Disk, Why Do They Call a Private a Private? Loesser", undated; 1 (Box 111, Item barcode 39002109975640)
        - "Noel Coward, demo, Sail Away", 1961 October 3; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978131)
          A list of contents is included with this audiocassette. Darby + Joan are also listed.
          Side A / Side B
          Come to Me (Mimi)
          I Am No Good at Love
          Sail Away
          Where Shall I Find Him?
          Beatnik Love Affair
          Later than Spring
          The Passengers Always Right
          Useful Phrases
          This is a Night for Lovers
          The Customer's Always Right
          Something Very Strange
          The Little Ones ABC
          When You Want Me
          Why Do the Wrong People Travel?
          This is a Changing World
          Bronxville
        - "The Magic of Mercer, M. Whiting et al.", NY audition, undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978149)
        - "Randy Newman", undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978156)
        - "Jerry Paris (Reagan) in California", 1983 August 22; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978164)
        - Brooks Kerr salutes Fats Waller, 1981; 1 (Box 112)
          This is a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
        - Guess Who's In Town: Bobby Short performs the Songs of Andy Razaf, 1987; 1 (Box 112)
        - Max Morath: Living a Ragtime Life, undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978172)
        - Songs of New York, East Side, West Side, All Around the Town, Cassette 1, 1984; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978180)
        - Songs of New York, East Side, West Side, All Around the Town, Cassette 2, 1984; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978198)
        - Alice Babs and Duke Ellington, Paris; "Money Jungle" - Duke and Mingus and Max, 1972; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610036)
        - Max Wilk - library, 2000 January 19; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610044)
        - "With a Song in His Heart: A Centennial Tribute to Lorenz Hart", NPR, 1995; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610051)
        - "Walden", Nancy Walker, A. Lyrics by Ira Gershwin; B. George and Ira Gershwin, Songbook #1", undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610069)
        - "Prohibition Blues" - Ring Lardner, undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610077)
        - "Foxy" - Score by Johnny Mercer, undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610085)
          A list of contents is included on this audiocassette.
          Many Ways to Skin a Cat
          Rollin' in Gold
          Money Isn't Everything
          Way Ahead of the Game
          S. S. Commodore...
          Talk to Me, Baby
          My Night to Howl
          I'm a Bon Vivant
          Run, Run, Run Cinderella
          Larceny and Love
        - Wang/Wilk - Kissinger, 1989 August 26; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610093)
        - "New Improved Bob and Ray #1 and #2, undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610101)
        - "New Improved Bob and Ray #3 and #4", undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610119)
        - Barbara Cook, "It's Better with a Band"; "Sweet Georgia Brown", undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610127)
          A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
          I Love a Piano (Berlin)
          It's Better with a Band
          Remember
          Come in From the Rain
          Chant La Vie
          Sing a Song with Me
          Them There Eyes
          Bernstein - Simple Song
          One Hand, One Heart
          Some Other Time
          I Can Cook, Too
          I Never Meant to Hurt You
          I Never Knew Men Cried
          The Ingenue
          If Love Were All
          Sweet Georgia Brown
        - "What a Beautiful Morning: A 50th Anniversary Tribute to Rodgers and Hammerstein's Oklahoma", NPR, 1993 March; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610135)
        - "John Fearnley, re: living Berlin, Lincoln Center", 1986 March 20; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610143)
        - Gracie Fields, Flanagan and Allen, Gingold, 1933; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610150)
        - Frank Loesser demos, undated; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610168)
          Includes fugue for tinhorns and Milton Delugg, "Most Happy Fella" - Maxine Andrews
        - Mercer- Merv Griffin Show ,Tony Bennett, Rosemary Clooney, Pearl Bailey, Mercer, 1975 March 17; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610176)
        - "The Colonel: An Affectionate Remembrance of Jack L. Warner", Friends of USC Libraries, Town and Gown, University of Southern California (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1979 March 4; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610184)
        - "The Colonel: An Affectionate Remembrance of Jack L. Warner", Friends of USC Libraries, Town and Gown, University of Southern California (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1979 March 4; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610192)
        - "Charles and Nancy Saxon", Westport, Part II, 1985 April 12; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610200)
        - Memo from Max Wilk (The Story of Oklahoma), 1990-1991; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610218)
          Elaine Steinbeck (1990) Live
          Richard Rodgers (tape)
          Oscar Hammerstein (tape)
          Celeste Holm (1990) Live
          Alfred Drake (1990) Live
          Agnes de Mille (tape)
          Song "Oklahoma!"
        - Mr. Tennessee Williams and Miss Audrey Wood, NY - DeMonn, Tandy Cronin, 1989 September 18; 1 (Box 139, Item barcode 39002104610226)
      - "Box #5: Show Tunes", 1950-2002
        - "Souvenir de Venise Natile, Parisian Suite Rysha Maynard / Duke [Ellington]; Andre Previn plays songs by V. D.", undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978214)
        - "A Noteworthy Occasion, tribute to Harold Adamson", 1971 June 6; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978214)
          A note is attached to this audiocassette. It reads: Dear Max, Thought you might enjoy these. Will phone when we return after March 10. Al Remson
        - "Louisiana Purchase, Carnegie Hall, I", 1996 June 23; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978222)
        - "Louisiana Purchase, Carnegie Hall, II", 1996 June 23; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978230)
        - "Maxine Sullivan Sings Harry Warren", undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978248)
        - "Paul Robeson Selections", undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978255)
        - "Zero Mostel: 'Harry Ruby's Songs My Mother Never Sang'", undated; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978263)
          I Was an Incubator Baby
          A Tulip Told a Tale
          Show Me a Rose
          My Dream of the south of France
          Father's Day
          Hold Me Thusly
          Fight on for Tannenbaum
          My Love is Waiting
          God Bless Everything in the USA
          Three Little Fishes
          There's a Girl in the Heart of Wheeling W. Va.
          He's Not an Aristocrat
        - "Broadway Applauds, Lincoln Center, PBS Radio", 1986; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978271)
        - "Ray Evans, NY", 2002 June 2; 1 (Box 112, Item barcode 39002109978289)
        - "Ya Got Class" sung by Michael Feinstein and Jay Livingston, undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611000)
        - "Al Hirschfeld", 1999 March 23; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611018)
          Hirschfeld talks about comedians, burlesque, EE Cummings, Bobby Clark NB, Lambert, Bea Lillie NB, Joe Cook, (Hopatcong.), Durante
        - "Max Wilk interview, BBC", 1999 April 15; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611026)
        - Candy is Dandy, Act I and II, undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611034)
        - Oklahoma!, Memo: from Max Wilk (Master), undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611042)
        - "Bert Williams, from Red Balaban", undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611091)
          Key to My Cellar
          Bring Back "W" Days
          Down in H.D. - "Preacher Low Down"
          Unlucky Blues
          Can't Trust Nobody
          Nobody's Business
          Oh Death Where is Thy Sting
          I'll Lend You Anything
          Woodman Spare that Tree
          It's Preposterous
          Adam was a Luck Guy
          Dr & Deacons
          Nobody #1
          Save a Little Dram
          Alimony Blues
          10 Little Bottles
          Misery Constantly
          Fortune Teller
          Barber Shop Chord
          Nobody #2
        - McCorkle explains her career with Terry Gross, Fresh Air, undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611059)
        - "McCorkle songs", undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611067)
          Includes "There's No Business Like Show Business" and "If I Only Had a Heart"
        - "2 Songs by Ring Lardner", undated; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611075)
          Includes notation: To: Max - From: Fred
        - The Mysterious Film World Of Bernard Herrmann, 1976; 1 (Box 113)
        - Roger Kellaway: Live at Maybeck Recital Hall volume eleven, 1991; 1 (Box 113)
        - "Something Wonderful: A Centennial Tribute to Oscar Hammerstein", National Public Radio, 1995; 1 (Box 113, Item barcode 39002104611083)
        - Elisabeth Welch: The Irving Berlin Songbook, 1988; 1 (Box 113)
        - Carmen MacRae, 1983; 1 (Box 113)
        - Mandy Patinkin Experiment, 1994; 1 (Box 113)
        - Cleo Laine & Jean Luc Ponty, undated; 1 (Box 113)
        - Julie Wilson: The Kurt Weill Songbook, 1988; 1 (Box 113)
        - Bobby Darin & Johnny Mercer with Billy May & His Orchestra: Two of a Kind, undated; 1 (Box 113)
        - The Song Is... Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart, 1986; 1 (Box 114)
        - Mel Torme & Cleo Laine "Nothing Without You", 1992; 1 (Box 114)
        - Rosemary Clooney: Do You Miss New York?, 1993; 1 (Box 114)
        - The Lady's In Love With You: Maxine Sullivan Sings the Music of Buron Lane, 1985; 1 (Box 114)
        - Linda Ronstadt: What's New, 1983; 1 (Box 114)
        - Memorial: Willie 'The Lion' Smith, 1950; 1 (Box 114)
        - The Roches, 1979; 1 (Box 114)
        - Weslia Whitfield: Live In San Francisco, 1991; 1 (Box 114)
      - "Box #6: Rare Music, (Musical Performers), Show Tunes, Radio and NPR", 1939-2000
        - "Harold Arlen Sings", undated; 1; 01:23:22; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610580)
        - "Saratoga, Original cast: Arlen/Mercer, Elgart", undated; 1; 01:09:39; Clicks, pops and static can be heard on the tape. There is a gap in the program from 54:35-55:36. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610598)
        - "Star: Julie Andrews, Act I", undated; 1; 00:41:14; Static can be heard. Clicks and pops are on the tape. The program is distorted at times. The program ends abruptly. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610606)
        - "Ogden Nash", undated; 1; 00:42:54; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. A buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610614)
        - "Regina" by Marc Blitzstein; Princess Zenobia Ballet, "On Your Toes", Warner Studio orchestra (for film version) (1939), undated; 1; Static, clicks and pops can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610622)
        - "Something Wonderful: A Centennial Tribute to Oscar Hammerstein", NPR, 1995; 1; 00:58:18; The program begins abruptly. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610630)
        - "Harburg by McCorkle", undated; 1; 01:33:37; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. The program begins and ends abruptly. Right-channel audio was recorded at a lower level beginning at about 49 minutes into the program. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610648)
        - "My Funny Valentine: E. Blair, All Things Considered, NPR", 2000 February 14; 1; 00:12:52 (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610655)
        - "Michael Feinstein, Jay Livingston CD", undated; 1; 00:17:06; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002104610663)
          Ya Got Class
          All the Time
          The Late Scene
          Mona Lisa
          TV Medley, "Bonanza" and "Mr. Ed"
        - "Michael Feinstein, 'Pure Imagination'", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974650)
          Pure Imagination
          Swinging on a Star
          Teddy Bears Picnic
          Because We're Kids
          Ferdinand the Bull
          Not Much of a Dog
          Lydia the Tattooed Lady
          The Dressing Song
          The Ugly Bug People
          When You Wish Upon a Star
          The Mole People
          Alice in Wonderland
          I'm Late
          The Unbirthday Song
          Aren't You Glad You're You
          I Like Old People
          Ten Feet Off the Ground
          Be Kind to Your Parents
          The Jitterbug
          Johnny Fedora A[?]
          Alice Blue Bonnet
          Angels on Your Pillow
        - "Michael Feinstein with Atlantic Symphony", conducted by Joel Silberman, undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974668)
        - "Beyond 42nd Street: The Harry Warren Story", host: Michael Feinstein, NPR, 1993 December; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974676)
        - "I Hear Music: An 80th Birthday Tribute to Burton Lane", host: Michael Feinstein, NPR, 1992 February; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974684)
        - "James P. Johnson: Lincoln Center", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974692)
        - "Jelly Roll Morton (Dick Hyman), James P. Johnson", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974700)
          Grandpa's Spells
          The Perfect Rag
          The Cave
          Fickle Fay Creep
          Pep
          Mr. Jelly Lord
          Black Bottom Stomp
          Buddy Boldens Blues
          The [Luger?] Breaker
          The Pearls
          Shreveport Stomp
          King Poter Stomp
          Charleston
          If I Could Be With You One Hour
          Caprice Rag. (solo)
          Running Wild
          A. Ginger Brown
          B. Old Fashioned Love
          C. Charleston
          D. Love Bug
          E. Snowy Morning Blues
          F. Open Your Heart
          Steeplechase Rag
          Jingles
          Eccentricity
          Carolina Balmoral
          Just Before Daybreak
          Carolina Shout
          You've Got to Be Modernistic
        - "Opening NIghts, Oklahoma! 1/5", BBC Radio 4, 1999 May 30; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974718)
        - "These Charming People (Kern) - Bolcomb, Moris, Morath", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974726)
          I Don't Think I'll Fall In
          Love Today
          You Never Know About Me
          Hang On to Me
          Feeling I'm Falling
          The Half of Lt. Dearie Blues
          Till the Clouds Roll By
          Let's Begin
          You Took Advantage of Me
          There's a Small Hotel
          The Babbitt and The Bromede
          Say So
          These Charming People
          Nobody Else But Me
        - "Candy is Dandy, White Barn Theatre", 1945 September 4-5; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974734)
          Low and Lazy
          April
          The Private Drug Room
          Just Like a Man
          Roundabout
          That's Him
          Very Very Rich
          Llama
          Animals Birds. Fish.
          Born too Late
          Sweet Bye and Bye
          Speak Low
          I'm Glad I'm Not a Man
          The Trouble with Women
        - "Girl Crazy", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974742)
        - "The Littlest Revue / (Nash Recites)", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974759)
          A list of contents for "The Littlest Revue" is included.
          Overture
          Madly in Love
          I Lost the Rhythm
          Dance Number (1)
          Third Ave. E1
          Fly Now and Pay Later
          Summer is a Comin
        - "Radio Composers Salute Berlin, Rare! WKOR", 1988 May 8; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974767)
          Composers listed include: Tom Jones, Harvey Schmidt, Sammy Cohn, Cy Coleman, Haswick, Bock, Burton Lowe, Charles Strouse, Jule Styne, Kay Swift, Caesar, Camden and Green, A. Bernstein, Kauder and Ebb, Arthur Siegel, and Alan Jay Lerner. Contents also list Irving Berlin songs, Jay Blackton interview, "Miss Liberty", and "God Bless America".
        - "A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum", cast album, undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974775)
        - Face the Music: A Century of Irving Berlin, 1988; 1 (Box 115)
          This audiocassette is commercial. It has not been digitized.
        - No, No, Nanette: Original Cast Recording, undated; 1 (Box 115)
        - " Rags, cast album", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974791)
        - " Bloomer Girl, cast album", undated; 1 (Box 115, Item barcode 39002109974809)
        - "Cole Porter: cut songs by Buster Davis", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610911)
        - "Singing in the Rain: Max Wilk", All Things Considered, UNM, 2000 May 30; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610929)
        - "One Touch of Venus, recorded on radio, (AM Railroads) radio", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610952)
        - "Dorothy Fields: Smithsonian recording", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610945)
        - "Sweet Bye and Bye, Born Too Late, That's Him (Weill)", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610937)
        - "Cole Porter, Can Can; Naura Hayden", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610960)
        - "Faith Middleton, Max Wilk, NPR", March 4; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610978)
        - "Sheldon Harrick, In My Own Lifetime, PBS", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610986)